<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Rooms>

<Room>
<Id>0</Id>
<Name>Starting Path</Name>
<Description>It's dark. 

You're standing on a grey gravel path. 

There's a signpost in front of you, it reads:
'N: Manor of Spook | E: Hither | S: Thither'</Description>

<N>1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>

<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>1</Id>
<Name>Manor Gate</Name>
<Description>There's a small boy and a black iron gate to the north. 

To your left and right there is a dense forest, into which you can't see very far.

There seems to be a name engraved into the gate but it's difficult to read.</Description>
<N>2</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>2</Id>
<Name>Manor Path</Name>
<Description>You're inside the manor gate. 

You're not sure if you should be here. 

A tree branch whips you as you walk near it, oof!

You feel as though somebody is watching you...</Description>
<N>3</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
<Items>stick</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>3</Id>
<Name>Manor Path v2</Name>
<Description>There are a few standing candlelamps along the path, but you can 
hardly see. 

Would it have killed this guy to get some solar path lamps from 'ye olde thyme
hardware store'?

And another thing, why is it so dark? It's 2:23 PM according to your iSunDial.

You hear something move to the east.</Description>
<N>4</N>
<E>5</E>
<S>2</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>4</Id>
<Name>Manor Entrance</Name>
<Description>There are steps leading to the manor - it's big, two stories, 'bout yay high.

The manor has two oaken doors and candlelamps on each side. 

One of the doors isn't quite closed.

There's a notice nailed to the door, it reads: 
'This is a notice nailed to a door'

A little existential, I suppose.

There's a window to the west.</Description>
<N>7</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>3</S>
<W>6</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>5</Id>
<Name>Maiden Scout</Name>
<Description>You are standing in a small offshoot of the path.

The noise you heard was a mouse.

There's a an abandoned Radio Flyer Red Wagon full of decrepit Maiden Scout 
cookie boxes. 

It looks like whoever owned this wagon left in a hurry. They left some of 
their belongings on the ground.</Description>
<Items>helmet</Items>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>3</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>6</Id>
<Name>Outside Window</Name>
<Description>There's a large window on the side of the house. 

It's covered with a curtain, but you can see something moving inside.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>4</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>7</Id>
<Name>Entryway</Name>
<Description>The entryway is large - there's is a door the the west, an ascending grand 
staircase, and a door to the east.

Along the walls there are: 
- Eight bookshelves 
- Four drawers
- Two chairs  
- One desk

What kind of 3-bit operation is this place? You wonder. </Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>9</E>
<S>4</S>
<W>8</W>
<U>50</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>quill</Items>
<Items>papyrus</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>50</Id>
<Name>Mad Laboratory</Name>
<Description>There are a myriad of whizzing, whirring machines and
dirty alchemical equipment. 

The floor is scattered with papers and feathers, and the walls plastered with drawings 
of what looks like Florence, Italy.
 
There is a man in a white robe hunched over a workbench. He's got wild, white hair, 
and is wearing one of those telescopic monocles. 
 
There is a duck sitting in a chair reading a newspaper. 
 
Neither of them raise alarm at your presence.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>7</D>
<Npcs>Father Duck</Npcs>
<Npcs>Mad Scientist</Npcs>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id></Id>
<Name></Name>
<Description></Description>
<N>0</N>
<E>0</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>0</W>
<U>0</U>
<D>0</D>
</Room>

</Rooms>
