<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Rooms>

<!-- Here be first floor rooms --> 
<Room>
<Id>0</Id>
<Name>Starting Path</Name>
<Description>It's dark. 

You're standing on a grey gravel path. 

There's a signpost to the north. It reads:

 --------------------------------------------
| N: Manor of Spook | E: Hither | S: Thither | 
 --------------------------------------------</Description>

<N>1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>

<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>1</Id>
<Name>Manor Gate</Name>
<Description>There's a small boy and a black iron gate ahead.

To east and west there is a dense forest, into which you can't see very far.

There seems to be a name engraved into the gate but it's difficult to read.

The path continues to the north.</Description>
<N>2</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
<Npcs>boy</Npcs>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>2</Id>
<Name>Manor Path</Name>
<Description>You're inside the manor gate. 

You feel like somebody is watching you - you're not sure if you should be here.

A tree branch whips you as you walk near it, oof!

There is a bunch of leaves and sticks to the north. 

You hear a noise to the west.</Description>
<N>26</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>1</S>
<W>25</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
<Items>stick</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>3</Id>
<Name>Manor Path 2.0</Name>
<Description>You're on the path again. 

There are a few standing candlelamps along the path, but you can hardly see. 

Would it have killed this guy to get some solar lamps from 'ye olde thyme
hardware store'?

And another thing, why is it so dark? It's 2:23 PM according to your iSunDial.

There is a bunch of leaves and sticks to the south. 

You hear something move to the west.

The path continues to the north.</Description>
<N>4</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>26</S>
<W>25</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>4</Id>
<Name>Manor Entrance</Name>
<Description>There are steps leading to the manor - it's big, two stories, 'bout yay high.

The manor has two oaken doors and candlelamps on each side. 

There's a notice nailed to the door, it reads: 

 -------------------------------------
| 'This is a notice nailed to a door' |
 -------------------------------------

A little existential, I suppose.

There is a window to the west

One of the doors isn't quite closed.</Description>
<N>6</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>3</S>
<W>5</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>5</Id>
<Name>Outside Window</Name>

<Description>There's a large window on the side of the house. 

It's covered with a curtain, but you can see something moving inside.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>4</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>6</Id>
<Name>Entryway</Name>
<Description>The entryway is large and bigly.

Along the walls there are: 
- Eight bookshelves 
- Four drawers
- Two chairs  
- One desk

What kind of 3-bit operation is this place? You wonder. 

There are doors to the east and west.

A grand staircase lay ahead.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>9</E> 
<S>4</S>
<W>7</W>
<U>50</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>quill</Items>
<Items>papyrus</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>7</Id>
<Name>Dining Room</Name>
<Description>There is a round wooden table in the middle of the room. 

There is a burning candle, a glass, an old book, and an old bottle of wine atop
the table. 

There's a fireplace along the eastern wall. 

It's warm. 

Along the walls there is a grandfather clock, and various tables.

There's a painting of a priveledged white male on beside the fireplace...

The eyes of the painting follow you as you move around. Hmm...

There are doors to the north, east, and west.</Description>

<N>11</N> <!-- north needs a room --> 
<E>6</E> 
<S>-1</S>
<W>8</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>

</Room>

<Room>
<Id>8</Id>
<Name>Servants Bedroom</Name>
<Description>A bedroom, next to a kitchen? Alright.

There's a burning candle atop a small wooden table. It looks old and crudely crafted. 

The bed looks appropriately bed-like.

You feel a cold draft.

There is a ladder leading down into a dark hole. 

There is a door to the east.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>7</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>75</D>

<Items>key</Items>

</Room>

<Room>
<Id>9</Id>
<Name>Kitchen</Name>
<Description>Knives and serving spoons hang from the far wall. 

It doesn't look like anyone has used this place in a while. 

There is an open box of frosted medeival-io's and a bag of kwik-e-barter donuts on the counter.

Gross, you hate foreign food.

There are doors to the north, east, and west.</Description>

<N>0</N> <!-- needs a room --> 
<E>10</E> 
<S>-1</S> 
<W>6</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>rat poison</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>10</Id>
<Name>Pantry</Name>
<Description>You clamber through a small, spring loaded door into a pantry.

It's chilly. 

There are wooden shelves with various sacks and widgets.

You eat a pretzal from an open bag. 

These pretzals are making me thirsty!

A spiralling stone staircase leads upwards.

There is a door to the east.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>9</W>
<U>51</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>heavy weight</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>11</Id>
<Name>Hallway</Name>
<Description>A long hallway along the back of the house.

There are no lights. 

There are windows along the northern wall, you can see that it's raining outside. 

You can just make out a door in the middle of the hallway, and doors at either end.</Description>

<N>11</N>
<E>9</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>7</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>

</Room>

<Room>
<Id>11</Id>
<Name>Courtyard</Name>
<Description>The rain stops as soon as you pass into the courtyard. 

The house looks smaller from back here. 

There's a drain pipe leading up towards an open window. The sounds and 
smells drifting out indicate that it must be the laboratory. 

The ground has been covered with dry cobblestones, they could use a good powerwashing. 

A small groundskeeping shed stands to the west - it's locked.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>11</S>
<W>12</W> 
<U>75</U>
<D>-1</D>

</Room>

<Room>
<Id>12</Id>
<Name>Groundskeeping Shed</Name>
<Description>The key opens the shed. 

There are a lot of tools in here. 

It smells like 'ye olde home depot' - cathartic.

There's a hole in the roof, and debris on the floor.</Description>

<N>-1</N>
<E>11</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>rubber hose</Items>

</Room>

<!-- Here be second floor rooms -->
<Room>
<Id>50</Id>
<Name>Mad Laboratory</Name>
<Description>There are a myriad of whizzing, whirring machines and dirty alchemical equipment. 

The floor is scattered with papers and feathers, and the walls plastered with
drawings of what looks like Florence, Italy.

An open window brings much needed fresh air. 

There is a man in a white robe hunched over a workbench. 

He's got wild, white hair, and is wearing one of those telescopic monocles. 
 
There is a duck sitting in a chair reading a newspaper. 
 
Neither of them raise alarm at your presence.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>6</D>
<Npcs>father</Npcs>
<Npcs>scientist</Npcs>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>51</Id>
<Name>Kitchen Attic</Name>
<Description>You're above the kitchen - it's a little claustrophobic up here. 

A chimney brush rests beside a crank and access panel mounted in the
wall, above where the stove would be in the kitchen.

The floor in front of the crank looks a little higher than the rest of the floor.

A spiralling stone staircase leads below.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>10</D>
</Room>
 <!-- Here be underneath rooms --> 
<Room>
<Id>75</Id>
<Name>Cellar</Name>
<Description>You're standing on dirt - it crunches beneath your feet. 

It looks like you're in some sort of cellar.

There are spiders scuddling along the floor and barrels stacked in the corner.

The air smells a little bit like your grandma. 

Why anyone would want access to a cellar from their bedroom is beyond you. 

There's a stone arch with an ethereal glow to the west and a ladder leading up.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>8</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<!-- here be portals, we still underneath tho --> 
<Room>
<Id>76</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #1</Name>
<Description>The portal hums as you walk through it. 

There's a sign on the wall, it reads: 

 -------------------------------------
|         Welcome to imgur. 	      |
| Climb up at any time to Restart ^_^ |
 -------------------------------------
 
You smell cheetos. 

There is a portal in each direction - they all look the same.</Description>
<N>8</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>78</S>
<W>77</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>77</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>77</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #2</Name>
<Description>The portal hums as you walk through it.

Not Copyrighted Morty: Aww jeez I don't know Rick, this seems kinda dangerous. 
Not Copyrighted Rick: Wubba Lubba dub-dub!!

You start craving szechuan sauce, it might be time to leave.

There is a portal in each direction - they all look the same.</Description>
<N>77</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>76</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>78</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>78</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #3</Name>
<Description>The portal hums as you walk through it. 

Alright honestly this portal stuff is starting to get old. 

You try to remember how you got here...west, west...no, north. East???

You start going a little insane. 

There is a door in each direction - they all look the same.</Description>
<N>50</N>
<E>78</E>
<S>77</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>79</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>79</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #4</Name>
<Description>The portal hums as you walk through it. 

You're back in the cellar again, at least some reposted version of it.

There's a sign on the wall, it reads: 

 ------------------------------------------------
|                 ~ Well done ~                  |
| You found the secret room where the bolts are! |
 ------------------------------------------------
 
There's something on the ground, it looks like bolts. How did they get here?

There is a portal in each direction - they all look the same.</Description>

<N>77</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>8</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>79</D>

<Items>pile of bolts</Items>
</Room>

<!-- Here be misc Rooms -->
<Room>
<Id>25</Id>
<Name>Maiden Scout</Name>
<Description>You are standing in a small offshoot of the path.

The noise you heard was a mouse.

There's a an abandoned Radio Flyer Red Wagon full of decrepit Maiden Scout 
cookie boxes. 

It looks like whoever owned this wagon left in a hurry. They left some of 
their belongings on the ground.

The path continues to the north and east.</Description>

<N>3</N>
<E>2</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>helmet</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>26</Id>
<Name>Pit of Dull and Annoying Spikes</Name>
<Description>Damnation - you fell into a trap!

You can just imagine the looks on your friend Bob's face when he finds out 
you were had by the oldest trick in the book. 

For shame.

There doesn't look like there is any way out. Please $ quit and try again.</Description>
<N>26</N>
<E>26</E>
<S>26</S>
<W>26</W>
<U>26</U>
<D>26</D>
</Room>

<!-- Here be a template 
<Room>
<Id></Id>
<Name></Name>
<Description></Description>
<N>0</N>
<E>0</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>0</W>
<U>0</U>
<D>0</D>
</Room>
-->

</Rooms>
