<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Rooms>

<!-- Here be first floor rooms --> 
<Room>
<Id>0</Id>
<Name>Starting Path</Name>
<Description>It's dark. 

You're standing on a grey gravel path. 

There's a signpost to the north. It reads:
'N: Manor of Spook | E: Hither | S: Thither'</Description>

<N>1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>

<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>1</Id>
<Name>Manor Gate</Name>
<Description>There's a small boy and a black iron gate to the north. 

To east and west there is a dense forest, into which you can't see very far.

There seems to be a name engraved into the gate but it's difficult to read.</Description>
<N>2</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
<Npcs>boy</Npcs>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>2</Id>
<Name>Manor Path</Name>
<Description>You're inside the manor gate. 

You feel like somebody is watching you - you're not sure if you should be here.

A tree branch whips you as you walk near it, oof!

There's a bunch of leaves and sticks to the north. 

You hear a noise to the west.</Description>
<N>26</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>1</S>
<W>25</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
<Items>stick</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>3</Id>
<Name>Manor Path 2.0</Name>
<Description>You're on the path again. 

There are a few standing candlelamps along the path, but you can 
hardly see. 

Would it have killed this guy to get some solar path lamps from 'ye olde thyme
hardware store'?

And another thing, why is it so dark? It's 2:23 PM according to your iSunDial.

There's a bunch of leaves and sticks to the south. 

You hear something move to the west.</Description>
<N>4</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>26</S>
<W>25</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>4</Id>
<Name>Manor Entrance</Name>
<Description>There are steps leading to the manor - it's big, two stories, 'bout yay high.

The manor has two oaken doors and candlelamps on each side. 

One of the doors isn't quite closed.

There's a notice nailed to the door, it reads: 
'This is a notice nailed to a door'

A little existential, I suppose.

There's a window to the west.</Description>
<N>6</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>3</S>
<W>5</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>5</Id>
<Name>Outside Window</Name>
<Description>There's a large window on the side of the house. 

It's covered with a curtain, but you can see something moving inside.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>4</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>6</Id>
<Name>Entryway</Name>
<Description>The entryway is large - there's is a door the the west, an ascending grand 
staircase, and a door to the east.

Along the walls there are: 
- Eight bookshelves 
- Four drawers
- Two chairs  
- One desk

What kind of 3-bit operation is this place? You wonder. </Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E> <!-- East needs room -->
<S>4</S>
<W>7</W>
<U>50</U>
<D>-1</D>

<Items>quill</Items>
<Items>papyrus</Items>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>7</Id>
<Name>Dining Room</Name>
<Description>There is a round wooden table in the middle of the room. There is a burning candle,
a glass, an old book, and an old bottle of wine atop the table. 

There's a fireplace along the eastern wall. It's warm. 

Along the walls there is a grandfather clock, various tables...

There's a painting of a priveledged white male on beside the fireplace...his eyes
follow you as you move around. Hmm...

There's a room to the north, east, and west.</Description>
<N>-1</N> <!-- north needs a room --> 
<E>6</E> 
<S>-1</S>
<W>8</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>8</Id>
<Name>Servants Bedroom</Name>
<Description>A bedroom, next to a kitchen? Alright.

There's a burning candle atop a small wooden table. It looks old and crudely crafted. 

The bed looks appropriately bed-like.

You feel a cold draft.

There is a ladder leading down into a dark hole. 
There is a door to the east.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>7</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>75</D>
</Room>

<!-- Here be second floor rooms -->
<Room>
<Id>50</Id>
<Name>Mad Laboratory</Name>
<Description>There are a myriad of whizzing, whirring machines and
dirty alchemical equipment. 

The floor is scattered with papers and feathers, and the walls plastered with drawings 
of what looks like Florence, Italy.
 
There is a man in a white robe hunched over a workbench. He's got wild, white hair, 
and is wearing one of those telescopic monocles. 
 
There is a duck sitting in a chair reading a newspaper. 
 
Neither of them raise alarm at your presence.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>6</D>
<Npcs>father</Npcs>
<Npcs>scientist</Npcs>
</Room>
 <!-- Here be underneath rooms --> 
<Room>
<Id>75</Id>
<Name>Cellar</Name>
<Description>You're standing on dirt - it crunches beneath your feet. 

It looks like you're in some sort of cellar. There are spiders scuddling along the 
floor and barrels stacked in the corner. The air smells a little bit like your grandma. 

Why anyone would want access to a cellar from their bedroom is beyond you. 

There's a stone arch with an ethereal glow to the west and a ladder leading up.</Description>
<N>-1</N>
<E>-1</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>8</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<!-- here be portals, we still underneath tho --> 
<Room>
<Id>76</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #1</Name>
<Description>As you walk through the portal you enter what looks like the dank may-may-verse.

There's a sign on the wall, it reads: 
Welcome to imgur. Climb up at any time to Restart ^_^

You smell cheetos, and angst - gross. 

There is a portal in each direction...they all look the same.</Description>
<N>8</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>78</S>
<W>77</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>77</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>77</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #2</Name>
<Description>Not Copyrighted Morty - Aww jeez I don't know Rick, this seems kinda dangerous. 
Not Copyrighted Rick - Wubba Lubba dub-dub!!

You start craving szechuan sauce - it's time to leave!

There is a portal in each direction...they all look the same.</Description>
<N>77</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>76</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>78</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>78</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #3</Name>
<Description>Alright honestly this portal stuff is starting to get old. 

You try to remember how you got here...west, west...no, north. East???

You start going a little insane. 

There is a door in each direction...they all look the same.</Description>
<N>50</N>
<E>78</E>
<S>77</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>79</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>79</Id>
<Name>Subterranean Portal #4</Name>
<Description>You're back in the cellar again...well at least some dank version of it. 

There's a sign on the wall, it reads: 
Well done - You found the secret room where the bolts are!

There's something on the ground, it looks like...bolts. How did they get here?

There is a portal in each direction...they all look the same.</Description>
<N>77</N>
<E>76</E>
<S>8</S>
<W>76</W>
<U>75</U>
<D>79</D>
<Items>pile of bolts</Items>
</Room>

<!-- Here be misc Rooms -->
<Room>
<Id>25</Id>
<Name>Maiden Scout</Name>
<Description>You are standing in a small offshoot of the path.

The noise you heard was a mouse.

There's a an abandoned Radio Flyer Red Wagon full of decrepit Maiden Scout 
cookie boxes. 

It looks like whoever owned this wagon left in a hurry. They left some of 
their belongings on the ground.

You can see the path to the east and to the north.</Description>
<Items>helmet</Items>
<N>3</N>
<E>2</E>
<S>-1</S>
<W>-1</W>
<U>-1</U>
<D>-1</D>
</Room>

<Room>
<Id>26</Id>
<Name>Pit of Dull and Annoying Spikes</Name>
<Description>Damnation - you fell into a trap!

You can just imagine the looks on your friend Bob's face when he finds out 
you were had by the oldest trick in the book. 

For shame.

There doesn't look like there is any way out. Please $ quit and try again.</Description>
<N>26</N>
<E>26</E>
<S>26</S>
<W>26</W>
<U>26</U>
<D>26</D>
</Room>

<!-- Here be a template 
<Room>
<Id></Id>
<Name></Name>
<Description></Description>
<N>0</N>
<E>0</E>
<S>0</S>
<W>0</W>
<U>0</U>
<D>0</D>
</Room>
-->

</Rooms>
